<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="/assets/xslt/rss.xslt" ?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="/assets/css/rss.css" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Walking with Grace</title>
		<description>»Feeling Responsive« is a responsive theme for Jekyll based on the fabulous foundation framework with beautiful typography and a bright color palette.</description>
		<link>http://www.walkingwithgrace.org.uk/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://www.walkingwithgrace.org.uk/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>First Delivery</title>
				<link>http://www.walkingwithgrace.org.uk/news/first-delivery/</link>
				<pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Judy and Suzy from Cuski welcomed the order and on 11th September 2015 the order was delivered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/mini_boo.png&quot; alt=&quot;The first Mini Boo&quot; width=&quot;300px&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/boxes_of_boos.png&quot; alt=&quot;Boxes of them&quot; width=&quot;305px&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After delivery Charlotte tied all the cards to the boxes of Cuski Mini-boos ready for delivery to the Unit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cards_1.png&quot; alt=&quot;Cards Explaining&quot; width=&quot;300px&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cards_2.png&quot; alt=&quot;On the boo boxes&quot; width=&quot;310px&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Monday September 15th, Charlotte, Scott and baby set off in a very loaded car to deliver the first 100 Cuski’s to the Neonatal Unit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/packed_1.png&quot; alt=&quot;Packaged and ready go&quot; width=&quot;226px&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/packed_2.png&quot; alt=&quot;A boot full&quot; width=&quot;400px&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Debbie Byran, Ward Manager along with a number of the staff who had helped look after Grace and Bella were on hand to receive the Cuski’s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/delivered.png&quot; alt=&quot;Delivered!&quot; width=&quot;600px&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All the staff who had seen Grace with her ‘boo’ agreed what a wonderful bonding and comforting aid the mini Cuski made.
Charlotte was thrilled to be able to present the very first Cuski Mini-boo to Baby Riley and his parents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/first_mum.png&quot; alt=&quot;First Family&quot; width=&quot;600px&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 class=&quot;t60&quot; id=&quot;other-posts&quot;&gt;Other Posts&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul class=&quot;side-nav&quot;&gt;

  

    
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.walkingwithgrace.org.uk/news/first-delivery/&quot;&gt;A Start &amp;middot; &lt;strong&gt;First Delivery&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.walkingwithgrace.org.uk/news/the-story-so-far/&quot;&gt;Walking with Grace our journey &amp;middot; &lt;strong&gt;The Story So Far&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    

  
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.walkingwithgrace.org.uk/news/first-delivery/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>The Story So Far</title>
				<link>http://www.walkingwithgrace.org.uk/news/the-story-so-far/</link>
				<pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
				<description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;the-story-of-walking-with-grace-and-the-cuski-mini-boos&quot;&gt;The story of ‘Walking With Grace’ and the Cuski Mini Boo’s.&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Grace and her twin sister, Bella should have been born at the RVI, Newcastle, but due to there being no intensive care cots available when they decided to arrive, 9 weeks early, their mummy was transferred to North Tees Hospital.
We knew the RVI provided Cuski comforters for their babies on the neonatal unit, unfortunately North Tees did not provide this service.
The girls Mamma (Maternal Grandmothers chosen name), tried to obtain Cuski’s for them but was unable to from the RVI and in desperation rang Cuski direct.  Here she spoke to the lovely Judy who was upset to hear the girls story and promised to have the Cuski Mini Boos in the post that evening, sending the next day recorded delivery. &lt;img src=&quot;/images/pink_cuski.png&quot; alt=&quot;Mini Boo&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And this is where the story begins….
Grace and Bella immediately took to their ‘boos’.  Mummy would carry the boos with her to ensure her scent transferred to them before placing them in the incubators with the girls. Grace in particular gained a great deal of comfort from her ‘boo’ as unfortunately mummy and daddy were not able to hold and cuddle her.  Grace was often found with her boo over her face, how she managed to do this was always a mystery, but time and time again that was where it was found.  When distressed the nurses would often place her boo by her face and immediately Grace would calm. 
Sadly we lost Grace after 47 wonderful days and Charlotte and Scott decided they wanted to give something back to the Unit who had supported them and their girls and it seemed very appropriate that the charity they set up in Grace’s memory –Walking With Grace, should provide Cuski Mini-Boo comforters to parents and babies who required long term incubator care to help them bond.
Initially fundraising and the very generous support of OrangeBus allowed the first order to be made. This generous support from OrangeBus and all those who sponsored Scott was for the Gatehead 10K Trail Run Sunday 15th August 2015, where Scott ran it in an amazing time of 1hour 6minutes and 45seconds. This was the first race that was completed with the sponsorship going to Walking with Grace. This was going to be used as a warm up and training run for the Kielder Run-Bike-Run which will take place on the 3rd October. There was an amazing sponsorship amount made from people Scott works with at OrangeBus, is was a total of £658 which his company matched at the first initial total given at £605 therefore raising a total of £1263.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 class=&quot;t60&quot; id=&quot;other-post&quot;&gt;Other Post&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul class=&quot;side-nav&quot;&gt;

  

    
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.walkingwithgrace.org.uk/news/first-delivery/&quot;&gt;A Start &amp;middot; &lt;strong&gt;First Delivery&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.walkingwithgrace.org.uk/news/the-story-so-far/&quot;&gt;Walking with Grace our journey &amp;middot; &lt;strong&gt;The Story So Far&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    

  
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.walkingwithgrace.org.uk/news/the-story-so-far/</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
